Walt Kuhn Family Papers and Armory Show
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Walt Kuhn Family Papers, 1859-1978, Series 4:; (Box 3-26, 32-35, OV 39-55; 25.8 linear feet)
  - Provenance Files, 1910-1964, 4.5:; (Box 11-13, 32, OV 42-44; 2.7 linear feet)
    - Oversized Tempera, Watercolor, Etching, Lithograph Records (1915-1938), undated, (Oversized material scanned with Box 13, F8) (Box 32)
    - Oversized Tracings of Artwork from Provenance Files, (Oversized material scanned with Box 11, F2, F5-6, F12-15, F17; Box 12, F1-4, F9, F13-16; Box 13, F4-5) (Box OV 42)
    - Oversized Tracings of Artwork from Provenance Files, (Oversized material scanned with Box 11, F3; Box 12, F11; Box 13, F5) (Box OV 43)
    - Oversized Miscellaneous Tracings of Artwork, (Oversized material scanned with Box 13, F9) (Box OV 44)
  - Other Projects1869-1897, 1910, 1922-1941, 4.6:; (Box 13-14, 33, OV 40-41, 45; 1.6 linear feet)
    Although the bulk of the Walt Kuhn Family Papers are related to Walt Kuhn's artwork and career as a painter, items in this series document Kuhn's other creative projects in theater, motion pictures, and graphic and interior design.
    In the 1920s, Kuhn designed and staged several vaudeville acts or "satirical ballets," which were performed in New York, Chicago, Atlantic City, and elsewhere. Included in this series are scripts, notebooks, sketches and drawings of costumes and stage sets, receipts, contracts, music, programs, a photograph, and a scrapbook. Notebooks contain sketches and production notes, contact information for theater people, and receipts signed by performers, among other notes. Scrapbooks contain clippings, programs, and one watercolor costume drawing. Other early theatrical writings and photographs can be found in Kit Kat Club and Penguin Club Records, and Kuhn describes his theater experience in detail in Walt Kuhn Letters to Family.
    In 1939, Kuhn wrote and directed a silent, educational motion picture film called "Walt Kuhn's Adventures in Art - Learning to See." Kuhn gave lectures with the film from 1939 to as late as 1947. Papers related to this project include drafts of scripts, notes, and visual materials used in the film, including intertitles, photographs and a collage. Drafts for another film, apparently never made, are also filed with scripts. Items relating to copyright of these projects are filed with Financial Records.
    From 1936 until 1943, Kuhn was employed by the Union Pacific (UP) Railroad Company through his connection with Averell Harriman, husband of Marie Harriman and UP's Chairman of the Board. He designed and decorated club cars and lounges for Streamliner trains, designed posters and brochures, and consulted for other projects. Kuhn's historically-themed club cars, "The Frontier Shack" and "The Little Nugget" involved two of his favorite historical themes, the old west and early stage comedians. Kuhn also designed graphics for UP's Sun Valley Lodge in 1937. Documents related to UP include blueprints, sketches, a poster, research notes, source materials, publicity, photographs, correspondence, pamphlets, tickets, sample materials, and notes. Related materials are filed in General Correspondence and Photographs and Scrapbooks.
    Theater and Motion Picture files are arranged by type of material, and UP files are arranged by project.
    This bulk of this series has been scanned. Copies have not been scanned and some oversized material, due to size and/or condition, has not been scanned. For publications, such as books, catalogs, and pamphlets, typically only the covers or covers and title pages have been scanned.
    - Theater (Box 13)
      - Scripts by Kuhn, 1923, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Scripts by Others, 1910, 1923-1928, undated, (2 folders) (Box 13, Folder 12-13)
      - Music, undated, (Oversized material housed in Box 33) (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Notebooks and Notes, 1922-1923, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
        (includes sketches)
      - Contracts and Receipts, 1922-1923, 1927-1928 (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Photograph, undated, (Oversized material housed in Box 33) (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Programs and Flyer, 1922, 1927, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Scrapbook, 1922-1923, (Oversized material housed in Box 33) (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Items Removed from Scrapbook, 1922-1923 (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Artwork, 1923, undated, (Oversized material housed in OV 45) (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - List of Theaters in the United States with Seating Capacity Over 1500, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Motion Picture, "Walt Kuhn's Adventures in Art: Learning to See" (Box 13)
      - Scripts, circa 1939 (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Photographs and Titles Used in Film, circa 1939, undated, (4 folders) (Box 13, Folder 24-27)
      - Photographs and Titles Used in Film (copies), circa 1939, undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Expenses, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Printed Materials, 1938-1939 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Interior and Graphic Design, Union Pacific Railroad Company (Box 13)
      - Frontier Shack (1936), 1936, 1938, undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - Frontier Shack (1936), undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
      - Frontier Shack (1936), 1885-1897, undated, (Oversized material housed in Box 33) (Box 13, Folder 33)
      - Frontier Shack (1936), 1937-1941, undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
      - Frontier Shack (1936), Copies, undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
      - Little Nugget (1937), circa 1937, (2 folders) (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
        (index cards and lists of comedians of the stage used for photos for Little Nugget)
      - Little Nugget (1937), undated, (3 folders) (Box 14, Folder 3-5)
      - Little Nugget (1937), Copies, undated, (Oversized material housed in Box 33) (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Little Nugget (1937), Blueprints, 1937, undated, (Oversized material housed in OV 40, OV 41) (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Little Nugget (1937), 1937-1948 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Little Nugget (1937), Photographs, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Little Nugget (1937), Photographs, 1948 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Little Nugget (1937), Photographs, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Little Nugget (1937), Duplicates, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Copper King (1938), circa 1938, (Oversized material housed in OV 40) (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Sun Valley Lodge, 1939, undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Sun Valley Lodge, Sketches, undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Sun Valley Lodge, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Sun Valley Lodge, Photographs of Rodeo, undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Sun Valley Lodge, 1937-1938, undated, (Oversized material housed in OV 45) (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Sun Valley Lodge, Printed Material, undated (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Golden Spike Days, 1939 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Hollywood Club Car, 1941, undated, (Oversized material housed in Box 33 and OV 41) (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Miscellaneous Notes and Writings, undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous Printed Materials, 1938-1940, undated (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Oversized Theater Music, (Oversized material scanned with Box 13, F14) (Box 33)
      (Original scores for "Lilies of the Field")
    - Oversized Theater Photograph, (Oversized material scanned with Box 13, F17) (Box 33)
    - Oversized Theater Scrapbook, (Oversized material scanned with Box 13, F19) (Box 33)
    - Oversized Frontier Shack Material, (Oversized material scanned with Box 13, F33) (Box 33)
    - Oversized Little Nugget Material (copies), (Oversized material from Box 14, F1-12) (Box 33)
    - Oversized Hollywood Club Car Material, (Oversized material scanned with Box 14, F21) (Box 33)
    - Oversized Little Nugget Blueprints, (Oversized material from Box 14, F7) (Box OV 40)
    - Oversized Copper King Blueprints, (Oversized material from Box 14, F13) (Box OV 40)
    - Oversized Little Nugget Blueprints, (Oversized material from Box 14, F7) (Box OV 41)
    - Oversized Hollywood Club Car Material, (Oversized material scanned with Box 14, F21) (Box OV 41)
    - Oversized Theater Artwork, (Oversized material scanned with Box 13, F21) (Box OV 45)
    - Oversized Sun Valley Lodge Material, (Oversized material scanned with Box 14, F16 and F18) (Box OV 45)
  - Financial Records, 1920-1961, 1972, 4.7:; (Box 14-15; 1 linear foot)
    This series contains records of the Kuhn family's financial assets and transactions. Types of material include account books, correspondence, legal documents, bills, and receipts. Sales of artwork are documented in Accounts of Moneys Received, Accounts of Paintings Sold, and to a lesser extent, Bills and Receipts. Also among the bills and receipts are insurance policies, travel expenses, lithography and publication expenses, and receipts for the shipment, framing, and photography of art works. Documents from the Walt Kuhn estate include a detailed appraisal made late in 1949 after his death, which lists several hundred works of art in his studio and on loan in various museums, among other property. A copy of the appraisal is annotated with notes of sales up to 1955.
    The file on Copyrights contains correspondence and copyright registration certificates for Kuhn's theater acts, publications and motion picture. Copyright information about Kuhn's translations of 1912 are filed with those publications in Armory Show Records. Information included in tax returns includes payments made to Kuhn's models, who are named as employees. Other files document more personal financial transactions. Notebooks filed under Assets summarize information about savings, mortgages, stocks, bonds, and other property.
    Arrangement is alphabetical by subject. Execution dates of artwork are given in parentheses after the file heading and should not be confused with record dates. Additional correspondence and receipts related to Kuhn's sales of artwork can be found in General Correspondence, Selected Gallery and Exhibition Files, and Provenance Files.
    This series has been partially scanned. Records not scanned include routine financial records such as leases, tax records, records of savings accounts and stocks and bonds, and utility bills, and some records relating to the will of Francis Kuhn.
    - Accounts of Moneys Received, 1923-1949, (2 volumes) (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Account of Painting Sales (1944-1949, 1952-1956), undated (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Assets, 1927-1953, (5 volumes) (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1925-1929, undated, (partially scanned) (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1930-1932, (partially scanned) (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1933-1936 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1937-1939 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1940-1941 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1941-1942 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1943-1944, (partially scanned) (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1945-1947, (partially scanned) (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1948-1950 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1951-1952 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1953-1957, undated (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Bond and Mortgage Guarantee Company, 1938, 1942 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Copyrights, 1923, 1938-1942 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Estates (Box 15)
      - Walt Kuhn, 1949-1955, (4 folders) (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
      - Francis Kuhn, 1882-1953, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
      - Francis Kuhn (copies), 1882-1953, (5 folders) (Box 15, Folder 7-11)
      - George Spier, 1923-1924 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Last Wills and Testaments of Vera and Walt Kuhn, 1925-1950 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Lawyer's Mortgage Company Reorganization, 1937-1949, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 14-15)
    - Leases, 1928-1961, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Materials, 1930-1953, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Notes of Personal Expenses, 1911, 1937-1949, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Savings Account Books, 1928-1960, (2 folders, 16 volumes) (Box 15, Folder 19-20)
    - Stocks and Bonds, 1920-1954 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Storage, 1936, 1941-1953 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Tax Records, 1936-1958, undated, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 23-24)
    - Utilities, 1934-1953, undated, (8 folders) (Box 15, Folder 25-32)
  - Notes and Writings, 1901-1972, 4.8:; (Box 17-19, 32; 4 linear feet)
    This series contains writings by Walt Kuhn, his family, and others, and notes relating to Kuhn's contacts, publications, artwork, and other activities. Types of material include index card files, address books, notebooks, manuscripts, typescripts, clippings, correspondence, and photographs.
    Card Files containing the Kuhns' scrupulous notes about people make up the bulk of this series. The files were kept in three separate alphabetical files with overlapping dates. They contain contact information, anecdotal details about shared meals, cocktail parties, or excursions, and cross-references to correspondence. Attachments such as clippings, correspondence, photographs, exhibition catalogs, and social announcements are common. Photographs and artwork found among the cards have been removed to separate folders, including images of Alan Burroughs, Sadakichi Hartmann, and Patsy Santo, and watercolor drawings by Lewis Barrington and Jean Oberlé. The original arrangement of the card file is idiosyncratic.
    Notes on Artwork include a list of Kuhn's artwork which sold at the auction of John Quinn's art collection in February 1927; many lists of artwork compiled for exhibition, shipping, and inventory; and detailed descriptions of early artwork written by Kuhn.
    Walt Kuhn's Notes and Notebooks include travel notes from Europe, the Western United States, and Maine, with a few sketches. Vera Kuhn's travel writings recount family trips to Nova Scotia from 1909 to 1912, and a trip to Europe in 1925.
    Miscellaneous Personal Notes range from shopping lists and recipes to more significant notes such as those about he disposition of artwork after Kuhn's death. Collection Notes are notes about the family papers written on envelopes. The items once contained by the envelopes were separated from their contents during initial processing and are now filed throughout the Walt Kuhn Family Papers.
    Other writings include manuscripts and visual materials from lectures given by Kuhn and Alfred Barr in 1934 about modern art collecting. Two articles about Kuhn published in Collier's in the 1940s are also filed here, along with related correspondence including letters from actress Dorothy Stickney, writer H.L.Mencken, and a number of Kuhn's former models. Photographs taken for the Collier's articles are filed with Photographs and Scrapbooks.
    Miscellaneous Writings by Walt Kuhn include an autobiographical essay and writings on modern art and artists. Kuhn's writings from the period of his final illness and hospitalization are also filed here. Writings about Kuhn include manuscripts by Alan Burroughs, Jeanne Robert Foster, Blanche Matthias, and Frank E. Washburn Freund. Also included are typewritten copies of published essays about Kuhn's work.
    Additional writings by Walt Kuhn are in Armory Show Records, Kit Kat Club and Penguin Club Records, and Other Projects. Significant writing about his artwork and techniques can also be found in his outgoing correspondence.
    The series has been partially scanned; card files and several address books have not been scanned.
    - Contacts (Box 16)
      - Card File 1, A-V; circa 1928-1948, (4 file boxes) (Box 16, Folder 1-4)
      - Card File 1, W-Z; circa 1928-1948, (1 file box) (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Card File 2, A-R; circa 1928-1948, (3 file boxes) (Box 17, Folder 2-4)
      - Card File 2, S-Z; circa 1928-1948, (1 file box) (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Card File 3, A-Z; circa 1928-1948, (3 file boxes) (Box 18, Folder 2-4)
      - Items Removed from Card File 1, 1930-1947 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Items Removed from Card File 2, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Items Removed from Card File 3, 1934-1947 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Address Books, 1943-1956, undated, (2 volumes) (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Address Books, 1930-1952, undated, (5 volumes; partially scanned) (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Mailing Lists, 1931-1963, undated, (2 folders) (Box 19, Folder 6-7)
      - Model Contacts and Contracts, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous Contact Information, 1937-1941, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Artwork Lists and Notes, Quinn Sale; 1927 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Artwork Lists and Notes, 1936-1965, undated, (2 folders; oversized material housed in Box 32) (Box 19, Folder 11-12)
    - Artwork Descriptions, undated, (Oversized material housed in Box 32) (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - "Story of the Armory Show" Notes, 1938-1939, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - 50 Paintings Notes, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Walt Kuhn Notes and Notebooks, 1936, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Vera Kuhn's Travel Writings, 1909 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Vera Kuhn's Travel Writings, 1910 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Vera Kuhn's Travel Writings, 1912 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Vera Kuhn's Travel Writings, 1925 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Brenda Kuhn's Travel Notebooks, 1935-1936 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Personal Notes, 1931-1959, (3 folders; oversized material housed in Box 32) (Box 19, Folder 22-24)
    - Collection Notes, 1920-1972, undated, (5 folders) (Box 19, Folder 25-29)
    - Contents of Safe Deposit Box, undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Lectures by Walt Kuhn and Alfred Barr, 1934 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Visual Materials for Lecture, undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Collier's Articles by and about Walt Kuhn, 1943, 1948, undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous Writings by Walt Kuhn, 1927-1948, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Writings about Walt Kuhn, 1922-1965, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Miscellaneous Other Writings, 1935, 1938, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Quotations and Statements about Art, undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Oversized Artwork Lists and Notes, (Oversized material scanned with Box 19, F12) (Box 32)
    - Oversized Artwork Descriptions, (Oversized material scanned with Box 19, F13) (Box 32)
    - Oversized Miscellanous Personal Notes, (Oversized material scanned with Box 19, F22 and F23) (Box 32)
  - Printed Materials, 1908-1987, 4.9:; (Box 20-23, 34, OV 40, 46-47; 3.9 linear feet)
    This series contains books, pamphlets, clippings, magazines, exhibition catalogs, invitations, announcements, art reproductions, programs, postcards, blueprints, and other printed ephemera gathered by Walt Kuhn and his family throughout their lives. Copies of published works by Walt Kuhn are filed here, as well as publications by friends and associates, including inscribed copies of works by Constantin Brancusi, Edwin Bjorkman, Frank Crowninshield, and Alice Garrett.
    Exhibition Catalogs are found for Kuhn and other artists. Catalogs are occasionally annotated with reactions to artwork or other notes. For Kuhn catalogs marked with prices and/or buyers, see 4.4: S elected Gallery and Exhibition Files. For catalogs of the Armory Show, see Armory Show Records.
    Clippings document Kuhn artwork and exhibitions, art institutions, art trends, collectors, other artists, Kuhn's other projects with the Union Pacific and theater, published life events of people known to the Kuhn's, articles written by friends, Walt Kuhn obituaries, and other miscellany. A significant portion of the clippings filed here are duplicated in other series.
    Many of the periodicals in this series contain reproductions of Kuhn's artwork. Promotional Ephemera for Kuhn's publications, lectures, and other appearances are also filed here, along with circus programs and posters, and mailings on a range of subjects. Other printed materials are scattered throughout the collection. See individual series descriptions for details.
    This series is partially scanned. Some blueprints, news clippings, exhibition ephemera, printed material containing reproductions of Kuhn's artwork, general promotional ephemera, and other printed material not directly related to Kuhn, have not been scanned.
    - By Walt Kuhn (Box 20)
      - Magazine Articles, 1947-1948, (Oversized material housed in Box 34) (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - A Little Bird Told Me,1908 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Fifty Paintings by Walt Kuhn (with Paul Bird), 1940 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - "The Story of the Armory Show," 1938 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - By Others, Bjorkman-Fraenkel, 1925-1937, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - By Others, Garrett-Oldfield, 1932, 1935-1936 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - By Others, Federal Emergency Relief Administration, 1933 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Blueprints of the Mrs. C.C. Rumsey Residence, 1926-1927, (Oversized material housed in OV 40) (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 1913-1940, (33 folders; oversized material housed in OV 46) (Box 20, Folder 9-41)
    - Clippings, 1941-1966, 1986-1987, undated, (30 folders) (Box 21, Folder 1-30)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1922-1923 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1927-1929 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1930, (2 folders) (Box 21, Folder 33-34)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1930-1931 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1932 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1933-1934 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1935-1936 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1936-1937 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1938-1944 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1945-1946 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1947 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1948 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1949-1952 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1953-1959 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, 1960-1969, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, Invitations, and Announcements, undated, (2 folders) (Box 22, Folder 8-9)
    - Other Exhibition Ephemera, 1941-1964, undated, (Oversized material housed in OV 46) (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Magazines, Newsletters, and Bulletins with Reproductions or Criticism of Kuhn Artwork (Box 22)
      - General, A-B, 1937-1953 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Art Digest, 1929-1948 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Art News, 1944 (Box 22, Folder 13)
      - General, C-I, 1927-1951 (Box 22, Folder 14)
      - Rainbow, 1920 (Box 22, Folder 15)
      - General, L-T, 1929-1948 (Box 22, Folder 16)
      - Time, 1953, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Other Magazines, Newsletters, and Bulletins, A-C, 1933-1956, (Oversized material housed in Box 34) (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Other Magazines, Newsletters, and Bulletins, F-M, 1935-1962 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Other Magazines, Newsletters, and Bulletins, P-W, 1931-1951 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Other Reproductions of Kuhn Artwork, 1931-1964, undated, (Oversized material housed in Box 34) (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Art Reproductions, 1947, undated (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Professional Organizations, 1948, undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Promotional Ephemera (Box 22)
      - Walt Kuhn, 1928-1945, undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
      - Circus Programs, 1937-1948, (3 folders) (Box 22, Folder 25-27)